we have a sarcasm And it's that Raquel bollo
tenemos un sarcas Y es que Raquel bollo
has made the comment Because
se ha pronunciado el comentario Porque
she doesn't work for the production company
además ella no trabaja en la productora
that you work for María Patiño you have to
que tú trabajas María Patiño le tienes
sell her your opinion I like
que vender tu opinión a mí me gusta que
things to be said upfront I want to use
se digan las cosas de frente quiero usar
SEO I want some action well and I wanted to
seo Yo quiero movida bueno y quería
show you now the second part of
poneros ahora la segunda parte del vídeo
Albert's video which is the one that I thought was
de Albert que es la que me ha parecido
brutal okay because I totally
bestial vale porque Estoy totalmente de
agree with this I have
acuerdo con esto
closed Albert's video man that
he cerrado el vídeo de Albert tío ese
was Albert's video Well I'll open it
era el vídeo de Albert Bueno lo abro
quickly also I want you
rápidamente además quiero que vayáis
all to go see the full video okay since
todos a ver el vídeo completo vale ya
we're here reacting
que estamos aquí reaccionando
I want you all to go to Albert's Channel
quiero que vayáis todos al Canal de
or subscribe give the
Albert o suscribáis le deis like al
video a like okay Since we're going to take advantage
vídeo vale Ya que vamos a aprovecharnos
of this information no and the thing is that he has
de esta información no y es que ha
spoken with Gloria Camila's lawyer
hablado con el abogado de Gloria Camila
and he has confirmed the suspicions that we
y le ha confirmado las sospechas que
had do you remember that I have been
teníamos os acordáis que os he estado
talking to you these past few days and explaining
hablando estos días atrás y explicando
what was happening with the issue of the second
lo que pasaba con el tema de la segunda
season of the docuseries I mean we're going to
temporada de la docuserie O sea vamos a
see the second season of the
ver la segunda temporada de la docu
docuseries at first there was one then they
serie en principio era una luego la
had to eliminate it then they had to
tuvieron que eliminar luego tuvieron que
record another and in the end Gloria  Camila
grabar otra y al final Gloria Camila
managed to stop her and now with all the
consiguió frenarla y ahora con toda la
shamelessness those documents
poca vergüenza esos documentos
surely that they did not want to hand over
seguramente que no quisieron entregar
okay
vale
those documents that they did not want to
esos documentos que no quisieron
hand over
entregar
now suddenly they have other
ahora de repente tienen otros documentos
new documents that they found in a
nuevos que se los han encontrado en un
drawer what do you think
cajón qué os parece
so there they are waiting because
entonces ahí están esperando porque
of course they cannot show anything specialized lawyers from Twitter and other television programs you can say whatever you want but what I have told you Gloria Camila and Rocío Carrasco my goodness this this video if I come out unscathed from this video because it is complicated because they are
porque es que es complicado porque son
very different cases to see I have managed to
casos muy distintos a ver he logrado
speak with Enrique trebolle lawyer as you
hablar con Enrique trebolle abogado como
know about Gloria Camila who is is
sabéis de Gloria Camila que está está
happy irony Morón
contento ironía Morón
we are talking about the Rocío Carrasco case
estamos hablando del caso Rocío Carrasco
in the name of Rocío the docuseries
en el nombre de Rocío la docuserie en
anyway Okay We have to go back in
fin Vale Nos tenemos que remontar en
this case to the lawsuit
este caso a la de a la demanda
filed by Gloria Camila I
interpuesta por Gloria Camila
think it was last September
creo que fue el pasado mes de septiembre
in court number 5 of Alcobendas
en el juzgado número 5 de alcobendas
okay
vale
Rosito announces a second season that
rosito anuncia una segunda temporada esa
second season Rosito the
segunda temporada rosito la fábrica de
TV factory that second season that was
la tele esa segunda temporada que se
canceled okay that second season of the
canceló vale esa segunda temporada de la
docuseries  canceled What happens is that since
docuser se canceló Lo que pasa que como
they are very proud and they want to
son muy orgullosos y son que quieren
move forward like a headless chicken, they are going to
palante como pollo sin cabeza pues van a
have a second season by force and
ser una segunda temporada por [__] y
as they can without going around in circles and
como puedan no dando dando vueltas y
somersaults no the second season that they
volteretas no la segunda temporada que
were going to broadcast was taking advantage of the
iban a emitir era aprovechando las
remaining images that had already been recorded
imágenes restantes que había ya grabadas
from the first they recorded 70 hours of
de la primera grabaron 70 horas de
recording they aired in the first
grabación se emitieron en la primera
season only what was about
temporada solo lo que era sobre los
Antonavi's children and the rest was about
hijos de antonaví y el resto Era sobre
the Mohedanos and it was the second season
los mohedanos y era la segunda temporada
okay
vale
how they started to carry it saying that they were going to
como empezaron a llevarla diciendo que
show some private documents
iban a mostrar unos documentos privados
of Rocío Jurado specifically a
de Rocío Jurado en concreto una
notebook with a manuscript
libretita con manuscrito
and more documents no that she had found
y más documentos no que había encontrado
rositos that had rosito and that left
rositos que tenía rosito y que dejaban
everyone in a bad light this to Ortega Canoa Gloria
mal a todos esto a Ortega Canoa Gloria
Camila to Gloria to Antonio well Gloria Camila
Camila a Gloria a Antonio pues gloria
sued but not a
Camila demandó pero no una demanda
normal lawsuit but it was some kind
normal y corriente sino era una especie
of precautionary measures a preliminary
de medidas cautelares una preliminares
okay the judge accepts it because she sees
vale la jueza lo acepta porque le ve
sense in the matter and asks Rocío
sentido al asunto y le pide a Rocío
Carrasco and the TV factory to
Carrasco y a la fábrica de la tele que
hand over those documents that she is going to release
entregue esos documentos que va a sacar
the series to see if she can show it or not
la serie a ver si lo puede enseñar o no
Because if  Gloria Camila can't show it, she
Porque si no lo puede enseñar Gloria
can claim
Camila puede reclamar
for weeks, Rocío Carrasco, her
durante semanas Rocío Carrasco y su
defense, and the TV factory give her the
defensa y la fábrica de la tele le dan
runaround. It's not that we don't know what
vuelta No es que no sabemos qué
document. Ah, I don't know what document she's
documento Ah no sé de qué documento nos
talking about. Ah, we don't have anything, and in the end what they
habla Ah no tenemos nada y al final lo
say is that no, that she has a
que dicen es que no que ella tiene
document, but that she has already destroyed them,
documento pero que ya los ha destruido
that she has nothing left, and that the docuseries
que ya no tiene nada y que la docu serie
only has a
lo único que tienen un documento pero
document, but that they are not going to show it, the two series, a document that has nothing to do with it, and
un documento que no tiene nada que ver y
that no, that she doesn't have any document, that they are
que no que no tiene ningún documento que
not going to show any document
ellos no van a mostrar ningún documento
in the series, therefore, the case is
en la serie por lo tanto el caso lo
archived,
archiva
they took it in reading and sold
ellos cogieron en lectura y vendieron
that file, and Sálvame, as if it had
ese archivo y el sálvame como si hubiera
won a lawsuit, is not archived,
ganado un proceso judicial no se archiva
okay, why do you say that there is
vale porque ustedes decir que no hay
no problem, that there is no
ningún problema que no hay ningún
document, then you have deceived the
documento entonces habéis engañado a la
audience because you have released some
audiencia porque habéis sacado unos
trailers and several programs in which you
tráilers y varios programas en los que
have announced that the second
habéis anunciado que la segunda
season is about some documents and
temporada trata sobre unos documentos y
some manuscripts, now in court,
unos manuscritos ahora en el juzgado de
yes, that she doesn't have any. Well, you
sí que no tiene ninguno Pues nada no
can't show anything because if now
podéis Mostrar nada porque si ahora de
suddenly they show some documents, they
repente muestran algunos documentos
would have lied to  the law what could
habrían mentido a la ley lo que podría
be procedural fraud Okay so they ca
ser estafa procesal Vale entonces ellos
n't show any documents they
no pueden enseñar ningún documento no
can't say now look at a
pueden decir ahora pues mira un
manuscript Well look at a will no
manuscrito Pues mira un testamento no
because they said they didn't have it
porque han dicho que no tenían
in the lawsuit the case is archived because it's
en la demanda el caso se archiva porque
already there because there is no document Well there is no
ya está porque no hay documento Pues no
case But now they do come out with some
hay caso Pero ahora sí salen con unos
documents yes there are cases and big let's
documentos si hay casos y gordo
see how they are going to put it together let's
a ver cómo se lo van a montar
see how they are going to put it together now
a ver cómo se lo van a montar ahora dice
Rocío Carrasco says that she has found the crazy one, I
Rocío Carrasco que ha encontrado el loco
mean they put together all the paraphernalia of the
o sea montan toda la parafernalia del
trailer of the containers I don't know but
tráiler de los contenedores no sé pero
who swallows this man it's the fans
quién se traga esto tío es que los fan
of these programs who are stupid okay I mean
de estos programas que son lelos vale o
who swallows that suddenly they make
sea quién se traga que de repente hacen
all this fuss if now they take out all the ones
todo este jaleo si ahora sacan todos los
from the containers I don't know what And suddenly coincidences coincidences
de los contenedores no sé qué Y de
In the containers they have found some
En los contenedores han encontrado unos
new documents Daniel Thank you very much
documentos nuevos Daniel Muchísimas
king for those 24 months suddenly it's
gracias rey por esos 24 meses de repente
that the containers have appeared
es que los contenedores han aparecido
with the documents of course This is not
con los documentos claro Esto no se lo
going to be brought to her by Gloria Camila or her lawyer and
va a traer Gloria Camila ni su abogado y
now Depending on whether they show something they are going to go to
ahora Depende si muestran algo van a ir
criminal court, in other words they
por lo penal o sea que otra vez les
have them again In other words, the docuseries
tienen agarrados O sea la docuseria
Gloria Camila has stopped her
gloria Camila la ha frenado
in this in this lawsuit that was it is a
en esta en esta demanda que era es una
lawsuit solely and exclusively to
demanda única y exclusivamente para
protect the privacy of Rocío Jurado
proteger la intimidad de Rocío Jurado
Although I insist that I make the observation
Aunque Insisto que yo hago la acotación
that there is also a part of
de que también hay una parte de
protection of privacy of her own
protección de intimidad de su propio
father of Ortega Cano
padre de Ortega Cano
is that lawsuit that is more than obvious
es esa demanda eso es más que obvio
they are throwing chicks no because it is that he
ellos tiran pollitas no porque es que lo
does it for José Ortega Cano How strange that
hace por José Ortega Cano Qué raro que
Ortega Canon has come as if to say that
Ortega Canon ha venido como diciendo que
Gloria wants to protect her father Yes of
Gloria quiere proteger a su padre Sí
course also what happens
claro también qué pasa
you have not filed a lawsuit when they have
tú no has puesto demanda cuando se han
messed with you and with trust what is the
metido contigo y con fidé cuál es el
problem in that in that also Gloria
problema en que en que también Gloria
Camila is partly stopping this so that
Camila en parte esté frenando esto para
nothing comes out that harms her
que no salga nada que perjudique a su
father What is the problem What is the
padre Cuál es el problema Cuál es la
oddity Here What is the shame
rareza Aquí Cuál es la vergüenza
they have some firefighter things we must not
tienen unas cosas de bombero no hay que
forget that it is admitted for processing By the
olvidar que es admitida a trámite Por la
judge because the judge despite the
jueza porque la jueza a pesar de las
explanations of Rocío Carrasco Rocío
explicaciones de Rocío Carrasco Rocío
Carrasco tries to avoid by all
Carrasco intenta evitar por todos los
means that this lawsuit prospers
medios que esa demanda prospere
the preliminaries I am not talking about trials
los preliminares no hablo de juicios
Here I am talking about the preliminaries it is started to
Aquí hablo de los preliminares se pone a
suspend she had  I remember that I
suspender ella tenía me acuerdo que
had a situation and they suspended it, she got it
tenía una situación y la suspendieron
suspended
consiguió consiguió que lo suspendieran
because it was like, well, what is it? No, I don't
porque era como que bueno que es lo que
know what papers
no que no sé qué papeles me está
my sister is asking me for. I don't have anything. I do
pidiendo mi hermana yo no tengo nada Yo
n't know anything. You know that there are some
no sé nada sabéis que hay unos
preliminaries, so that is taken before
preliminares entonces eso se lleva ante
the judge and the judge is the one who decides in the
la juez y la juez es la quien decide al
end. What actions must be
final Cuáles son las acciones que hay
taken? No, in this case, she is
que acometer no en este caso ella
filing this lawsuit, Gloria Camila,
interpone esta demanda Gloria Camila
because she
porque
wants to find out somehow
quiere enterarse de alguna forma de
what the
cuáles van a ser los documentos
official documents in the name of Rocío Jurado are going to be that are
oficiales a nombre de Rocío Jurado
going to be shown in that series
que se van a mostrar en esa docu serie
of agreements to try to protect her, to
de acuerdo para intentar protegerla en
protect the privacy of her mother, Rocío
proteger la intimidad de su madre Rocío
Carrasco. In the first case, there are two orders
Carrasco en una primera hay dos autos
here from the judge, one from the 16th and another from the
aquí de la jueza uno del 16 y otro del
29th of October.
29 de octubre
There are two orders from the judge because there is a
hay dos autos de la jueza porque hay una
first appearance of Rocío Carrasco,
primera comparecencia de Rocío Carrasco
which says that since she is the
que lo que dice es que como ella es
universal heir, okay, she does not have to
heredera universal vale no tiene por qué
show
Mostrar
any documents. And in one of the orders,
ningún documento y en uno de los autos
this judge, no, Alberto, this judge, I want to
esta jueza no Alberto esta jueza quiero
remember, court number 5 of Alcobendas,
recordar juzgado número 5 de alcobendas
what she tells him is that the privacy of
lo que le dice es que la intimidad de
a dead person is
una persona muerta
not inherited.
no se hereda
that is not inherited no matter how much
que no se hereda por mucho heredera
you are a universal heir, the privacy of a
universal que seas la intimidad de una
dead person is not that you say well
persona muerta no es que digas bueno
since I am a universal heir I can
como soy heredera universal yo puedo
do whatever I want with the
hacer lo que me da la gana con la
privacy of that person because I am
intimidad de esa persona porque yo soy
the universal heir and what
la heredera universal y lo que le dice
the judge tells you is no ma'am, this does not work
la jueza es no señora esto no funciona
like that you have inherited the
así usted habla heredado la propiedad
intellectual property intellectual work of the artist
intelectual obra intelectual del artista
That is how it is properties or whatever but
Eso es así propiedades o lo que sea pero
privacy is a concept that is not
la intimidad es un concepto que no se
inherited So if someone gets it and
hereda Así que si alguien consigue y
especially because as well They are
sobre todo porque como bien Ellos están
claiming and making fun of them it also
reclamando y se burlan de ellos también
affects the privacy of others these
afecta la intimidad de los demás
are private things between Rocío Jurado and
son cosas privadas entre Rocío Jurado y
the rest of her relatives who are
el resto de sus familiares que están
still alive hence the judge
vivos todavía de ahí que la juez
admitted the procedure in those preliminaries and
admitiera trámite en esos preliminares y
requested that exhibition of documents
pidiera esa exhibición de documentos
because she considered that this privacy was not
porque Consideró que esa intimidad no se
inherited and that Gloria Camila was within
heredaba y que Gloria Camila estaba en
her legal and judicial right to claim
su derecho legal y jurídico de reclamar
that exhibition of documents okay And in
esa exhibición de documentos vale Y en
that exhibition of documents
esa exhibición de documentos
no document is exhibited, that is to say
no se exhibe ningún documento es decir
those three mediaset the production company the
esa tres mediaset la productora la
factory of television and Rocío Carrasco
fábrica de la tele y Rocío Carrasco
mediaset the network says that nothing has reached her
mediaset la cadena dice que no le ha
producer says that nothing has reached her
la productora dice que no le ha llegado
and Rocío Carrasco presents a single
nada y Rocío Carrasco presenta un único
document despite the fact that the court says
documento a pesar de que dicen sede
in the words of Enrique Trebolle that she
en palabras de Enrique trebolle que no
has no more documents Because she has destroyed many of them, in other words, she hands over
tiene más documentos Porque muchos los
a document that
ha destruido o sea entrega un documento
was a document that she would surely
que era un documento que seguramente
hand over with all the malice in the
entregaría con toda la mala leche del
world that it would be a document that would surely
mundo que sería un documento que seguro
affect Ortega Cano and leave him in a
que afectaba a Ortega Cano y lo dejaban
bad light, her intention is that this
mal lugar la intención de ella que ese
document would come to light and be discussed
documento saliera la luz y lo comentaran
in one of these programs, a lot to
en alguno de estos programas mucho para
hit her with an eight, Ortega surely won,
pegarle una ocho Ortega ganó seguramente
okay, in other words, metaphorically, okay,
vale o sea de forma metafórica vale
a document that had nothing to do
un documento que no tenía nada que ver
with what they were going to release in the documentary and she
con lo que iban a sacar la documental y
says that she has nothing more, that she has
dice que no tiene más que los ha
destroyed them, that she has no more, okay, now
destruido que no tiene más vale ahora de
suddenly some documents have been found
repente se ha encontrado unos documentos
and the only document that she hands over,
y el único documento que entrega
what does she hand over is a document that
qué entrega es un documento que no le
neither the judge nor Gloria Camila's lawyer had asked for, what
había pedido ni la jueza ni el abogado
happens is that with
de Gloria Camila lo que pasa es que con
this action, with the fact of not handing over
esa acción con el hecho de no entregar
any documents because she claims and
ningún documento porque ella esgrime y
that is going to be important, that either she does not have them
eso va a ser importante que o no los
and since she does not have them, they cannot be
y como no los tiene no se pueden
shown because we are not talking
mostrar porque aquí no estamos hablando
about her here, she can have the
de ella puede tener los documentos
official documents in the name of  Rocio Jurado who
oficiales a nombre de Rocío Jurado que
wants as if she has 20 containers
quiera como si tiene 20 contenedores
full we are not talking about her
llenos no estamos hablando de que los
owning them or not owning them we are
posea o los deja de poseer estamos
talking about what they want to do or what they
hablando de que quieren hacer o que
want to use or they want to make
quieren usar o se quieren hacer públicas
certain information public for their
determinadas informaciones para un
own business which is a documentary series and that is
negocio propio que es una docusería y
where the Sister says careful
ahí es donde la Hermana dice cuidado
before that happens I want to see what is
antes de que eso pase yo quiero ver lo
going to be shown to protect
que se va a mostrar para proteger la
my mother's privacy Thank you but in the
intimidad de mi madre Gracias pero al
end
final
the lawsuit did not prosper because in a certain
la demanda no prosperó porque en cierta
way since Rocio Carrasco did not show
manera como Rocío Carrasco no mostró
anything then Gloria could not take the
nada pues gloria no pudo tomar las
pertinent actions it
acciones pertinentes
is filed because there is no case because it is
se archiva porque no hay caso porque se
assumed that well Rocio I mean I
supone que bueno Rocío o sea es que me
love that they sell it as a victory
encanta que lo vendan como una victoria
for Rocio Carrasco Rocio Carrasco gave it
para Rocío Carrasco Rocío Carrasco
a blow they put the reading You are
varapalo pusieron el lectura Estás
talking about or rather in any case the one who wins
hablando o sea en todo caso la que gana
Gloria has destroyed and to stop the
Gloria ha destruido y a frenar la
documentary series that has been going on for a year and has not been broadcast It has
docuseria que lleva un año y no se emite
been almost a year that it should have been broadcast and it is
Casi ya un año que se tenía que haber
not broadcast and you have
emitido y no se emite y la habéis
recorded it 800 times different it
grabado ya 800 veces diferente
is filed because it is not going to remain
se archiva porque no se va a quedar
open, in other words the cases in the courts
abierto o sea los casos en los juzgados
one case goes ahead or  archive it is
un caso sale adelante o se archiva se
archived because it is not going to stay open
archiva porque no se va a quedar abierto
not forever it is archived I
no para toda la vida se archiva me
love it because because in any case if
encanta porque porque en todo caso de
Camila wins it would be a victory but of
ganar sería una victoria Camila pero
course it is archived because it is assumed that she
claro se archiva porque se supone que no
has nothing
tiene nada
that she could have had at that time to
que podía tener en ese momento para
try to stop the series that she already
intentar parar la serie que ya algo algo
achieved something okay because the times have been what they have
logró vale porque los tiempos han sido
been like precautionary measures
los que han sido como medidas cautelares
not like to say okay like now
no como para decir vale como ahora yo
with this documentation as a
con esta documentación como de entrada
precautionary measure from the start before I have not
medida cautelar antes de que yo no haya
reviewed all this and such the series
revisado todo esto y tal la serie se
stops this could not be done because she
para esto no lo pudo hacer porque ella
Rocío Carrasco did not show anything she did not exhibit
Rocío Carrasco no mostró nada no exhibió
anything and evidently Gloria Camila
nada y evidentemente gloria Camila no
cannot file a lawsuit something that has not
puede interponer una demanda algo que no
happened that is why we said let's
ha sucedido por eso dijimos van a
wait to see what happens with the
esperar a ver qué sucede con la docu
docuseries okay But what happens is
serie vale Pero qué pasa
that they in court they in court
que ellos en sede judicial ellos en sede
declared that they did not have any
judicial declararon que no tenían ningún
official document from Rocío Jurado
documento oficializado de Rocío Jurado
with which nothing was going to be shown
con lo cual no se iba a mostrar nada
okay to do it to do it
vale
would imply a crime of procedural fraud
implicaría un delito de estafa procesal
a crime punishable in a severe way
un delito penado de forma severa una
procedural fraud But in addition I can already
estafa procesal Pero además ya os puedo
tell you exclusively that Enrique
avanzar en exclusiva que Enrique
trebolle told me yesterday
trebolle me comentó ayer
that they are willing Gloria Camila
que ellos están dispuestos Gloria Camila
is willing to go through criminal proceedings,
está dispuesto a ir por la vía penal
which will go through criminal proceedings. In other words, if
que irá por la vía penal
any document is shown that they consider should have been filed
algún documento que ellos consideren que
beforehand,
antes tendría que haberse
regardless of that
independientemente de esa estafa
procedural fraud, that possible
procesal que de esa posible estafa
procedural fraud, if they consider that there is
procesal si ellos consideran que hay
any document
algún documento
that invades the privacy of Rocío Jurado
que invada la intimidad de Rocío Jurado
and is shown in that docuseries, one two
y se muestre en esa docuserie un dos
three, answer again a will, one two
tres responde otra vez un testamento un
three, answer again a will, they will
dos tres responda otra vez un testamento
go through criminal proceedings and there will be a complaint
Irán por la vía penal y habrá querella
from Gloria Camila. If that happens, okay,
de Gloria Camila Si eso se produce vale
confirmation. I mean, I'm already telling you,
confirmación O sea ya os lo digo
official confirmation, of course, and that's where they come in. I
confirmación oficial claro y ahí entran
insist, uh, any official document
insisto eh cualquier documento oficial
of Rocío Jurado that is shown in the
de Rocío Jurado Que se muestre en la
docuseries
docuserie
and taking into account that the bait
y teniendo en cuenta que el cebo
is already that will prior to the one that was
ya es ese testamento anterior
revoked in favor of another
a que se revocó a favor de otro
will, showing, for example,
testamento Mostrar por poner un ejemplo
a will
un testamento
of that type
de ese tipo
would imply, according to Enrique Trebolle, in addition
implicaría según Enrique trebolle además
to the crime of procedural fraud, that
de un delito de estafa procesal que
Gloria Camila would defend herself with an
Gloria Camila se defendería con una
action, they are going to remind me of what happened with Marlon,
acción van a me recuerda lo de Marlon
man, I mean, they are going all out, they are going
tío o sea van allá por todas van allá
all out and it doesn't matter to them that Gloria
por todas y les va da igual que Gloria
Camila wants to report them and they are going to
Camila les quiera denunciar y van a
take it and they are going to say that  the documents
[__] y van a decir que los documentos
no what the documents did not have that they have
no lo que los documentos no lo tenía que
found it now in which
la han encontrado ahora en el
a twin brother has brought them from I do
que se los ha traído un hermano gemelo
n't know where you know or literally it goes to him it does not matter to him it does not matter to him I
de no sé dónde sabes o sea literal le va
tell you
da igual les va a da igual ya os lo digo
that it will not matter to him and they will take out
yo que le va a dar igual y van a sacar
the will and they will say with all their
el testamento y van a decir con todo su
Papo and with all their ball that they will
Papo y con todo su pelota que serán
find the drawers what they are
encontrar los cajones lo que están
saying already in the intro
diciendo ya en la intro
now it will depend on the judge that you
ahora ya dependerá de los juez que
touch and he takes it Seriously or he does not
toques y se lo toma En serio o no
take it Seriously not
se lo toma En serio no
criminal through the criminal way okay it happens
penal a través de la vía penal vale pasa
with that document and it happens with others
con ese documento y pasa con otros
because in the end the feeling that
porque al final la sensación que sí que
the lawyer does have It is that in some way it has been
tiene el abogado Es que de alguna forma
played with justice
sí que se ha jugado con la justicia ya
since days later we had the parade
que días después teníamos la cabalgata
the removals the containers they
las mudanzas los contenedores ellos
stopped It is that this was like that look and
frenaron Es que esto fue así mira y
also I have a video but I do not
además yo tengo un vídeo pero no me
remember what it is called I have a video
acuerdo cómo se llama Yo tengo un vídeo
where In addition I mark it for you with dates okay
donde Además te lo marco con fechas vale
the docuseries already in the trailer for the
la docu serie ya en el tráiler de la
second season
segunda temporada
in the trailer for the second of the
en el tráiler de la segunda de la
second season it shows you previously
segunda temporada te saca imágenes
unpublished images that are her with the Pink suit
inéditas que son ella con el traje Rosa
sitting but she is talking  Ortega Cano
sentado pero está hablando Ortega Cano
those images do not belong to the first
esas imágenes No pertenecen a la primera
season also the corner of the trailer
temporada además la esquina del tráiler
shows unpublished images that that
pone imágenes inéditas
that docuseries the second
ese esa esa docu serie la segunda
season was already recorded they were not going to
temporada ya estaba grabada no la iban a
record it again it was the Brute that they had not been
grabar otra vez era el Bruto que no
able to take advantage of in the first
habían podido aprovechar en la primera
season I have said many times the
temporada lo he dicho muchas veces la
first season was 60 or 70 hours
primera temporada fueron 60 o 70 horas
of recording they themselves have said it
de grabación ellos mismos lo han dicho
many times of which they have
un montón de veces de los cuales han
broadcast half
emitido la mitad
because half has been broadcast because the
porque se ha emitido la mitad porque la
first season was Antonio VI and Two
primera temporada fue Antonio vi y dos
Sons now the rest of the interview
hijos ahora el resto de la entrevista
that was talking about Ortega Cano and the
que era hablando de Ortega Cano y de los
Mohedanos and so on with the story that
mohedanos y demás con el cuento de que
Rocío Carrasco is the best and the one who is most
Rocío Carrasco es la mejor y la que más
right the best and whoever does not
razón tiene la más buena y quien no la
believe it because he is an abuser is also worth it that
crea porque es maltratador también vale
was the second season with some
eso era la segunda temporada con algunos
clicks that they were going to add
clics que iban a Añadir
from
de
the documents and so on that they were going to
los documentos y demás que iban a
show no then Gloria Camila files
mostrar no entonces Gloria Camila pone
that lawsuit and what they do is
esa demanda y ellos lo que hacen es
throw away everything she had and it is no longer valid we do not
tirar todo lo que tenía y ya no vale no
have a document we are not going to show
tenemos documento no vamos a enseñar
anything it was bait but we do not have it we do not
nada era un cebo pero no tenemos no
know what document you are talking about
sabemos de qué documento nos habla
so
entonces
that lawsuit is archived
esa demanda se archiva
if not  I'm wrong, November 11th, I
si no me equivoco un 11 de noviembre os
'm speaking from memory, but
estoy hablando de memoria pero
check it and put it in the
comprobarlo usted y ponérmelo en la caja
comment box so you can see if I pay attention
de comentario para que veáis si atiendo
and do my homework when I talk about the subject,
y hago los deberes cuando hablo del tema
that lawsuit is not valid, when Rocío
no vale esa demanda ya cuando Rocío
Carrasco says that she doesn't have them, that she doesn't
Carrasco dice que no los tiene que los
have the documents, that she didn't
documentos no tiene nada que no lo
destroy them, they're not going to release anything, that lawsuit
destruyó no van a sacar nada esa demanda
is filed, it's filed because there's no case, there are no documents, there's no
se archiva se archiva porque no hay caso
case, but of course it's
no hay documentos no hay caso pero claro
filed without a document because there aren't any, you can't go
se archiva sin documento porque no los
and file another lawsuit, I
hay no puedes [__] y sacar otra demanda
mean, you can't, other documents, okay, it's
o sea no puede otros documentos vale
filed, I think that file is on
se archiva creo que ese archivo un 11 de
November 11th, check it, if it's not an 11th it's
noviembre comprobarlo si no es un 11 es
a 13th or something like that, okay, but I think it was
un 13 o algo así vale pero creo que fue
November 11th,
un 11 de noviembre
in January they suddenly release a program
en enero de repente sacan un programa
called
que se llama
the January trailer program, what was it called, what was it called
el de enero de los trailers cómo se
in January, the trailer
en enero lo del tráiler cómo se llamaba
program, what was it called, I don't remember the name of the trailer program that we were
programa de los trailers que estuvimos
here in the afternoon relating it
aquí por la tarde relacionándolo
Monte Alto, it was the special they did
Monte alto era el especial que hicieron
later with the house, but the
después con la casa pero el programa es
special program that they did in the afternoon was
especial que hicieron por la tarde era
another one with the  trailers on the m-30 I
otro con los tráilers por la m-30
don't remember what the last
no me acuerdo cómo se llamaba el último
trip was called The last trip, okay, in that
viaje El último viaje ese vale en ese
program in that program if you watch my
programa en ese programa si veis mi
video in that program they already say that they have been
vídeo en ese programa ya dicen que han
preparing for 90 days, in fact,
preparando hecho
90 days preparing that program
90 días preparando ese programa
if we are talking about January,
si estamos hablando de enero
which I think was like the end of January
que creo que era como a finales de enero
or around there,
o por ahí
90 days
90 días
coincided with the date that they had
coincidían con la fecha que habían
archived the Gloria Camila case,
archivado lo de Gloria Camila
the math is like that, it has been done little has been
las matemáticas son así hecho poco se ha
commented on but I'm telling you that they
comentado pero ya os lo digo yo que
should take it more into account November,
deberían tenerlo más en cuenta noviembre
December and January, that is, those were the 90
diciembre y enero o sea fueron los 90
days, it is archived,
días se archiva se archiva la demanda de
Gloria Camila's lawsuit is archived and Rocío Carrasco
Gloria Camila y se quedan Rocío Carrasco
and the TV factory remain. Now how do we
y la fábrica de la tele ahora cómo lo
do it
hacemos
now how do we do it, okay? In fact,
ahora cómo lo hacemos vale De hecho
before it was archived, before it was
antes de que se archive antes de que se
archived, there was an interview where Rocío
archive había una entrevista que Rocío
Carrasco is going crazy, her duty is to be
Carrasco da va bestia deber de ella es
with Boris and Aguirre at a
con está con Boris y Aguirre en un
parade or something like that. I think it was, there is no
desfile o algo así Creo que era no salen
photo and in that interview she says that she is
una foto y en esa entrevista ella dice
already recording it,
que ya lo está grabando
that the recordings are starting and it's a
que están comenzando las grabaciones y
lie, there was no recording
es mentira no había ninguna grabación
because they have recorded it now
porque la han grabado ahora
what is it?  what happens is that when
qué es lo que pasa que cuando se archiva
the lawsuit filed by Gloria Camila is filed, they
la demanda que pone Gloria Camila se
meet and say, well now what do we do?
reúnen y dicen Bueno ahora qué hacemos
We have eliminated the Rosa suit
hemos eliminado lo del traje Rosa
and the document we cannot remove because we have already
y documento no podemos sacar porque ya
said here that there are no documents and
hemos dicho Aquí que no hay documentos y
then they invent all the
entonces se inventan toda la
paraphernalia of the trailers and in those
parafernalia de los trailers y en esos
90 days they prepare everything in those 90 days
90 días lo preparan todo en esos 90 días
the containers are opened, they are checked and
los contenedores se abren Se revisan y
everything else, the containers are not opened
demás a los contenedores no se abren
there live and she suddenly, I mean,
allí en directo y ella de repente O sea
imagine she is opening the
imagínate que está abriendo los
containers and a tiger thong of
contenedores y sale un tanga de tigre de
Rocío Jurado comes out,
la Rocío Jurado
that has been checked before starting to
eso se ha revisado antes de empezar a
record to open it, do you understand? In fact, I
grabar a abrirlo me entiende de hecho me
remember that there would be a container and you can see
acuerdo que habría un contenedor y se ve
how well hung everything without covering the
como bien colgado todo sin tapar los
suits, you are not a suit, I
trajes no sos traje ya
remember that we caught that in addition,
me acuerdo que pillamos que además los
Anabel Dueñas had already worn the suits
trajes ya se los había puesto Anabel
in some shows, okay, I
Dueñas en algunos espectáculos vale o
mean, they prepare this whole rigmarole that they have
sea se prepara todo ese tinglado de que
brought the containers from the warehouse, she
han traído los contenedores del almacén
has opened it. There, everything, no, the little house is
la la ha abierto Allí todo no la casita
re-enacted, Monte Alto, no. Why is that done?
reasen Monte alto no Para qué se hace
Well, now suddenly,
eso pues para ahora de repente otros
three months later, they come out saying that they have
tres meses después salir diciendo que de
suddenly found some documents there
repente han encontrado allí unos
and this has  past
y esto les ha pasado
and this has happened to them for having played and having
y esto les ha pasado por haber jugado y
wanted to get the most money
haber querido sacar el máximo dinero
possible because as I think it
posible porque como bien dijo creo que
was Albert himself who said in a, I don't know
fue el propio Albert en un en un no sé
if it was a video or a live broadcast,
si fuera un vídeo o en un directo
this could have been handled in a,
esto se podía haber despachado en un
this could have been handled in
esto se podía haber despachado en un en
an interview
una entrevista
at most in two or three parts of an
como mucho en dos o tres partes de una
interview, it would have lengthened everything
entrevista lo hubiera alargado todo lo
that was done in the documentary and what is being
que se hizo en el documental y lo que se
said, what they want to say in the
está lo que se quiere decir en la
second season, without selling it, without
segunda temporada sin venderlo sin
baiting it, they would have let it
cebarlo lo hubieran lo hubieran largado
all out and now for Gloria Camila she
todo y ahora ya por Gloria Camila
would have sued whatever she wanted to
hubiera demandado lo que hubiera querido
sue but now it's easier to ask for
demandar pero ya es más fácil pedir
forgiveness than permission, now that she's
perdón que permiso ahora como se ha
started baiting it, how they've started baiting it, well, they have
puesto a cebarlo como se han puesto a
no choice but to stop, they've
cebarlo pues ya no les queda otra que
gotten themselves into this mess, they've
ha frenado se han metido en el lío este
already said in court that they don't
ya han dicho en la justicia que no
have a document to get out, now they
tienen documento que sacar ahora no
can't get away with it with documents, they've
pueden salirte con documentos han
caught you hand and foot
pillado de pies y manos
[Music]
[Música]